The stock market's sitting at all-time
highs. Is it a good time to buy right
now? Should you wait? What does history
show you? And what are some
opportunities if you're looking for
individual stocks to buy right now?
You can see the S&P 500 all-time highs
here, 7723. We closed over 7700 for the
first time in history a day or two ago.
You can see Nasdaq's up slightly, while
the Dow and the S&P are down slightly.
And if you're looking at buying at the
S&P 500 at all-time highs,
you might think, well, that's a risk,
right? You want to wait for a pullback.
And of course, I'm never here to tell
you what to do with your money, but
history says the risk is overstated.
So, if you look at this going back to
1950, and I posted this on X,
history says no, that it's not
necessarily risky to buy here.
Of course,
nobody knows for sure, but since 1950,
buying at new highs produced smaller max
drawdowns than buying on any random day,
or even during pullbacks, corrections,
or bear markets. So, 1 month, you got
the stats here.
Why is that exactly? I think it's
because the market kind of puts a new
floor in. It doesn't mean it can't go
below it.
But historically, going back to 1950,
often times you get a new all-time high,
you kind of put a new floor in it, and
it's going to depend on a lot of things,
macro and earnings and GDP and all these
things that we talk about all the time,
especially in the private community.
And as we go through this video, we'll
talk about the K-shape economy and some
of the risk of that, right? And you're
going to see bifurcation in different
stocks. And I'm just sharing the facts
here, you know, waiting for a dip
doesn't always mean that you reduce
downside. That's the point. And the main
point is that time in the market still
beats perfect timing or trying to time
the market. Generally, that's what
traders do, and it doesn't work very
well. So, some crazy earnings. I've been
covering as much as I can for you here
as well as in Discord. We've got
earnings from Mercado Libre, Celsius.
We've got Uber yesterday, AppLovin,
DataDog, and more. We're going to talk
about those and more. If you look at one
of the fired up wealth favorites we
bought and shared back at $75 a share.
You'll remember this high time smaller
cap semiconductor company. Now it's a
$17 billion market cap. In fact, the
52-week high was 900 bucks. It's 661
right now, but it's up 21.74%
today after a really strong earnings
report. So, congrats to any bulls that
bought SiTime at $100 or less. You've
done quite well with the stock.
Now, you don't care about that one. You
want to find opportunities cuz you might
have missed SiTime. What are some other
stocks that maybe I'm buying, the
community's buying?
I bought some Mercado Libre today. Of
course, that's just what I'm doing with
my money. You have to do what's best for
you, but earnings I thought were really
strong. I'm going to explain why the
stock is down 7% after earnings. If you
look at this, GAAP EPS of $9.19 beat by
25 cents.
Revenue $10.17 billion. This is a new
record.
Almost 50% year-over-year revenue growth
that beat by $410 million.
And so, you could look at some of the
stats and say you know, originally the
shares were up 3.4%
and then they came down.
Why is that exactly? Let's talk about
it. So, in Discord in the Fired Up
Wealth Community portfolio, I shared
some of these stats with you
and I also shared
we'll talk about that one later, but
Mercado Libre, all right?
This is a 50% year-over-year topping $10
million for the first time.
You can see that.
Overall, really strong report. What's
going on? Let me break it down in simple
terms, right?
MELI, it wasn't a cheap stock to begin
with especially on traditional valuation
metrics.
For a long-term investor,
these quarterly fluctuations matter
less. This for me is a 10-year hold. I'm
holding this for 5 or 10 years. Buy,
hold, and monitor. This is me monitoring
my investment. In fact, I bought some
more today.
And I do think that Mercado Libre has
tremendous TAM and opportunity, and
that's why I'm investing it with with my
money. All right?
So, what exactly is going on? Well,
first of all, it's important to
understand how these percentages work.
So, when you see 6.7%, this is the
operating EBIT's margin
for this quarter.
Gross profit margin TTM, if you look at
like, for example, on
Let's just show you Seeking Alpha really
quick. If I go into here and I go into
profitability, you're going to see this
gross profit margin TTM at 49.47%.
Okay? So,
when I look at this number,
which is what you're going to see in
these highlights,
right here, 6.7%,
the market doesn't like that number,
right?
And I'm going to explain to you why, but
gross profit margin TTM, a rough
educated guess here because the company
doesn't publish the exact split, but I
think e-commerce is probably 38% to 42%,
so let's just call it 40%. Fintech,
you know, roughly 58% to 65%. The blend
is about that 50% you saw on Seeking
Alpha.
The gross margin is going to tell you
the profitability of the actual products
or service. Operating EBIT margin, if
you're not an accounting major, is going
to tell you what's left over after
running the business, people, marketing,
tech, overhead, etc. So, management, if
you listen to earnings, and it's
important if you are an investor to
listen to earnings calls,
management's deliberately choosing
growth and long-term competitive
strength. This is a huge opportunity
when you think of total addressable
market with Latin America. It's got to
build out that logistics ecosystem,
right?
And management is deliberately choosing
growth and long-term competitive
strength over near-term profitability.
And then said it right on the call.
The results of a deliberate choice to
continue prioritizing investment over
near-term profitability. So,
prioritizing investment over near-term
profitability.
In short, though, Wall Street hates
spending, investing over short-term
profits. They'd rather see short-term
profits. You see this over and over
again. I've been investing over 25
years. I'm telling you, Wall Street
doesn't like to talk about 5 years from
now. They want to talk about 5 weeks or
5 months.
As someone who owned Amazon for many
years, this is very similar. Amazon had
to spend a ton of money on capex to
build out its ecosystem, its logistics
infrastructure.
The big difference here is that Amazon
had AWS, Amazon Web Services. MELI
doesn't have cloud services. In fact, a
big chunk of MELI's business runs on
AWS.
But this is a long-term story, in my
opinion. This thesis is as bullish as
ever. This is a very strong report. Did
add a little bit more, just a nibble
here. And you can see the buy on your
screen from Mercado Libre.
So, looking at a chart, I'll tell you
where,
you know, what I see, the possibilities.
This stock was up to 2645 here. This was
July of 2025.
So, just in 1 year, it's come back.
I believe it's an opportunity. Of
course, you have to always do what you
think is best for your money, build a
blueprint, right? But here are your
updated fibs. These are Fibonacci's.
When you look at technical analysis, 99%
is fundamentals. That's going to be
quantitative and qualitative analysis.
The last 1% after you put in the
homework, you've researched the stock,
the financials, the management, all
that, competition, SWOT analysis, right?
Bear case, bull case.
Then you're going to come in, you're
going to look at this chart.
And you're going to try to see where
better entry and exit points are. That's
the point of TA, technical analysis, not
to look at a chart and buy off the
chart.
So, based on that, you're going to have
an idea of what you think the stock is
worth, what you think it might be worth
as a long-term investor in the future,
right? And of course, nobody knows for
sure, but you put in the work, and the
harder you work, the luckier you get.
The luckier you get. But this updated
fibs S1 1759,
that's just slightly lower than we're at
right now. It's trading at 1777. S2
1713. S3 1640. Could it go lower? Could
it go under 1500? It could. And I would
love that cuz I would I would buy
heavily in that price range.
I personally like Mercado Libre, but
it's a long-term investment, so it says
right here, 2035 hold. If you're buying
this for a quick buck, you probably
should avoid it. All right? So, this is
not this going to be a quick hitter.
Now, next, Celsius just reported
earnings this morning, and you can see
non-GAAP EPS of 36 cents, missed by 6
cents. That's no good.
Revenue 817.9 million,
also missed. This is a double miss.
The guidance also isn't stellar. The
stock is down 16% under $25 a share.
And you can see the growth is only
10.6%.
Overall, this was not a great earnings
report. So, if you are a Celsius bull,
it's important to understand what's
happening, and I'm going to go back into
Discord in the fire up wealth community
portfolio channel. I posted this this
morning.
So, Celsius shares fell sharply.
And you can read all this. Pause your
screen if you'd like.
The community portfolio does own a small
position. That Mercado Libre, by the
way, it's about 4%. I want it to be a
core. It's The goal is 5%.
Celsius, it's more of a spec position.
Generally, spec for us is 1%. They're
small positions.
So, you're building out a blueprint.
You're going to have maybe 10% in spec
and have
a bunch of stocks, 10 or 20, not just a
couple. And I know some people are going
to be listening with $500 accounts and
say it doesn't make sense. I get it. Do
what's best for your money. I'm just
sharing what I do with my money and how
this community portfolio works.
This portfolio is roughly 550 grand. We
started it new with zero
zero dollars in 2022.
But this is a 0.85% of the portfolio. So
you could add a little bit if you wanted
it could even be like a 1 and 1/2%
position if you wanted to.
I'm not buying it right now. I haven't
added this morning.
But it I I do think it could be an
opportunity if you don't own it as an
entry point.
At the same time, I kind of share my
thesis here.
And this is going to segue into the next
thing, but
overall this is a brutal quarter.
Management's discussing 2027 on the
call. They really lack confidence in the
rest of this year. I don't think it's
going to be a fast recovery without a
catalyst. In other words, I don't think
this is just going to
be a V-shape recovery kind of tomorrow
and and bounce back to over $30. It
could because the thing about it you
have to remember, 60 to 70% of
short-term movement in stocks is about
sentiment and momentum.
As a long-term investor, we're not using
60 to 70% of sentiment and momentum in
our decision-making. And we know that it
could take time for stories to play out.
So as a long-term investor, this might
be something like, "Hey, I'm willing to
potentially buy some shares and maybe
add it if it goes lower." We call it
dollar cost averaging.
But it might not fit your blueprint. And
this is not a stock for everybody
because this is consumer focused and
it's more of a speculative type player,
right? When you think of secular growth
trends and technological trends, I mean,
energy drinks aren't really that. Is it
a secular trend? I mean, you can see
Monster stock. Uh you might be
surprised, you know, people that don't
understand Monster.
If you look at the stock,
the max performance on this, it's up
49,000%. This beats a whole lot of tech
stocks out there.
You know, if I look at like 5 years, of
course, 93% a lot of that growth comes
from going way back here when it was a
penny stock. And I'm not saying that
that this is something that you can find
nowadays because of how IPOs work, but
the point being is that this stock has
crushed it. You know, even if I look in
the last like 10 years, it's done very,
very well, right? So,
I'm not saying that Celsius has to
necessarily do that, but I am saying
there is a path there for growth and for
a stock to make money. We've seen it
with Monster.
Be careful of the trap of well, Nvidia
did it and they're 5 trillion, so AMD
has to be that, too. I'm not saying that
Celsius has to be Monster. And if you
look at the market share, of course,
it's it's going to have a market share,
but you have huge competition with
Monster
as well as Red Bull and others, right?
So, lots of competition. Now, Pepsi does
own 11% of this, but what I really want
to focus on uh um Wingstop and Celsius.
To me,
it's telling me that the consumer is not
doing as well as most people think.
And it's really explaining the type of
economy we're in.
And I want to talk about that so you
kind of understand. Now, when you invest
in any any type of commercial
or consumer-focused stocks, I should
say, B2C,
you know, consumers are fickle and
what's popular today might not be
popular popular tomorrow and you have to
be careful with these kind of stocks,
you know, like restaurants. If you've
ever owned a restaurant, I'm a part
owner of a restaurant. I've owned other
restaurants in the past. They're
generally not good investments.
Consumers are very fickle. Restaurants,
the the fads change. It's a very
difficult industry. Margins are very
tight, generally. And you look at
Wingstop, this reported earnings
recently and it did beat on EPS by 16
cents,
but it missed on revenue and the worst
part here, only 6.5% growth. And even
worse, domestic same-store sales
declined
4% to 6%.
So, what is that telling you? Because
you can also look at McDonald's and you
can see
McDonald's gains even after comparable
sales momentum phase in Q2. Well,
McDonald's is a little bit different
because people buy this for a 2.68%
dividend. Very different type of
investor, right?
A DJI type investor, that's not really
going for growth, they're going for the
income. Like that passive income
strategy after you've accumulated money
and so forth.
So, if you look at this comparable sales
for McDonald's up 0.8% in the US versus
0.9% consensus, but this isn't great
growth, right? But you're having
actually negative with Wingstop and it
comes back to the demographic, it comes
back to a lot of people that are
maybe buying this, they don't have as
much money. And the reason they don't
have as much disposable income is
because oil prices are higher. When it
costs $70 to fill up your gas tank
versus 50, that's 20 bucks less to spend
on energy drinks, on McDonald's, on
Wingstop, and so on. So, the demographic
both
the type of customer that they're
targeting, especially with Wingstop for
example, as well as when you think of
the financial demographics, we have
what's known as a K-shaped recovery.
So, a K-shaped recovery, what that is is
it's an economic state
where different parts of society or
industries move in opposite directions
at the same time. High earners and asset
owners climb the upward arm of the K.
So, if you you make a lot of money and
you've been investing a lot of extra
disposable income into the stock market,
it's just compounding and going
you know, up this direction
versus the other way if you're lower
income and you're not actually So, stock
market's going higher, tech stocks are
going higher, you've got high earners
and asset owners climbing upwards in
that arm of the K through thriving
investments, while lower-income groups
and labor-dependent sectors slide down
due to persistent inflation, tighter
budgets, and not benefiting from things
like the stock market.
And this is why if if you are new to
investing, this is why investing can
change your life. It's It's never a
guarantee, but if you look at the
history of the stock market in the in
the history over the years, generally
speaking, it's been a good investment if
you're buying the S&P 500, buying
high-quality stocks, and holding them
for the long term.
If you don't know my background, I come
from a situation where I didn't grow up
with money.
And being a multi-millionaire now, it's
all because of the stock market. And
I've also done real estate investing as
well, but the stock market is the
simplest wealth creation tool for me
because it's not going to call me at
4:00 in the morning and tell me, you
know, that I have to go unplug the
toilet, you know, that the toilet's
clogged, or the water heater exploded,
or you know, whatever.
Lots of things happen as a as a as a
a landlord, and you probably know if you
own any rental properties, it's
definitely not passive income, right?
Stock market, anybody can download an
app, and you can buy stocks. The problem
is is most of the time you're not
educated, you buy the wrong stocks, and
you lose money. And the stock market
really is designed
to take your money if you let it. If
you're FOMO chasing at the wrong time,
you're using options trading and margin
and derivatives, those are all things
that are dangerous that I personally
wouldn't do as a new investor, all
right? But this is a K-shape economy
recovery. Talking about like technology,
retail, and software services going up,
travel, entertainment, food services,
hospitality going down, and this is what
you're seeing.
And with oil prices being as you know,
accelerating higher for a while there
because of the Middle East tension, that
is going to put pressure on inflation.
It makes everything more expensive. It
also tells the Fed, "Hey, we can't lower
interest rates because inflation's
sticky. We might actually have to raise
interest rates, which would make the
market gyrate, right?"
So, I mean, McDonald's stock is holding
up a little better, but this again, this
is more of a dividend type stock, 2.71%.
So, I'm not trying to put them in the
same bucket. I'm just comparing
consumer. The consumer has less money to
spend. They're going to spend less money
at McDonald's,
at with Celsius, buying a $3 energy
drink, you know, with Wingstop, you just
don't have the money to do it, right?
So, that's important to cover.
AppLovin also had earnings. GAAP EPS,
$3.77,
beat by 2 cents.
Revenue, $1.92 billion. That's up 52.4%,
but it missed by $20 million.
So, I look at this and I say,
"What's going on here?
Why is the stock down?" It's down 20%
right now.
I'll get to that in a second. Before I
do that, I I know I already covered
MELI. I do want to cover Celsius and
Wingstop just to show you
where the possibilities are on the
chart. You know, with Celsius, you look
at this thing, it was 100 bucks, and we
say,
"Fundamentals are 99%, technicals are
1%." This is a great example where FOMO
chasing just doesn't end well. I
remember
a VIP member bought the stock really
cheap down here, really cheap somewhere,
and he had a big position. It was a
large percentage of portfolio, and we
don't like having big concentrations.
I said, "You know, you could consider
maybe taking some profits on this at 100
bucks. It's pretty expensive, and you
know, just looking at it, it it it
doesn't seem like something." And of
course, he sold it, and it did fall, and
then it popped back up, and he was
probably getting nervous, but then this
happened, right?
Well, if you really love the company,
you can always buy some more shares at
$24, but when if when it's ahead of
itself and it's parabolic, this is a
parabolic chart. These are what we call
air pockets. This
generally does not end well when you
have a trend line down here and the
stock's up here. So, you usually want to
trim this to half shares, or you know,
trim out of it completely if you want,
but if you still want it in your
blueprint, you might trim it to half
shares.
So, you might sell 2/3 of it or
something, you know, depending on how
you're managing it with that blueprint
and the and those
But now it's all the way down here. Is
it a buy? Well, it could be an
opportunity, like I said, for you know,
a new position.
The S3 Fibonacci is $22.33. With a bit
bit more weakness, I think you could
easily break $20 a share. So, right here
is the S3, $22.33.
And it could bottom anytime. It could
hold up around 25, but it's important to
understand the possibilities. If you
were to buy some at 25 and it went to
19, you shouldn't be insanely shocked
because I'm telling you it's a
possibility.
Wing stock, you know, or Wingstop,
Wingstop stock.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh fundamentals, this I just said this
on August 4th before chart day and said
fundamentals have broken down. That same
store sales growth is decelerating.
Their target target demographic is being
impacted. Again, that K-shaped economy.
The S3 is $95. I could easily see it
under 100. Now, buyers are coming around
120. Again, you have to DCA it. And it's
tough cuz you buy some at 120, you know
that the S3 is 95. So, if I bought some
at 120 and it went to 95, I wouldn't be
shocked because that's a possibility in
the chart and it's a very bearish setup
overall, right? It's probably going to
fade lower. It doesn't have to fade
lower. And if you look at this, it did
bottom out at 116 in April. Could it
retest something similar or maybe $5
higher? That happens all the time. It's
going to come down to your conviction.
Do you like this company? Do you like
this stock? I will tell you though, the
fundamentals, guys, do not look great.
They don't look really really good at
all. So, you know, th- this is not good
on Wingstop. You know, I I have probably
a little bit more confidence in Celsius
than Wingstop at this point. But neither
of them are like, "Hey, I have to go out
and run and buy this." I'm not I'm not
adding either right now. If they go a
little bit lower, maybe, and I'll keep
you posted, of course, in Discord, like
I always do, right?
But I do want to cover AppLovin.
It's down about 20%. I also want to talk
about Uber and DataDog and a couple
others.
AppLovin, right?
If I look at this 52% growth, you say,
"Well, it's cuz it's really expensive."
Well,
this is a tough one.
Profitability matrix, you know, if I
look at the metrics on this, 88% gross
profit margin TTM is A+ profitability on
Seeking Alpha, net income per employee
4.47 million. This is higher than
probably anything you'll see. This is
even higher than Nvidia.
And these numbers are off the charts,
like
just to give you an example, Nvidia,
it's bringing in about $3.8 million per
employee.
So, $3.8 million for Nvidia. Amazon, cuz
it has a lot of people with the retail
side of it,
only $85,000 net income per employee.
And then I look at AppLovin,
it's bringing $4.47 million.
With amazing gross profit margin, 88%.
The growth, 30% 60 6% I just showed you
50%.
And you say, "Well, it's got to be too
expensive." Well,
I mean,
it's not dirt cheap or anything, but a
26 gap forward, this actually has gap
profitability.
It even has a PEG gap TTM of 0.39. Under
one is generally good.
The price to sales, the forward is a 17,
so these numbers get a little goofy
sometimes with especially with anything
that has kind of SaaS or recurring
revenue like this does.
But generally speaking, if I look at 30
and 60 and 50% growth and a 26 gap
forward P/E ratio,
it it piques my interest, right?
And yet, the stock on AppLovin is down
14% in the past year.
It is up 470% in the past 5 years, so
you could say maybe it's profit taking,
but I'll tell you what I think it is.
Let me do that after I show you the
chart.
Cuz I always seem to forget. And I'm I'm
doing this live, guys. Like I'm not
editing at all. It's not scripted. I
just have some things up that I want to
talk about, and I'm trying to go on that
order. But, AppLovin,
here's the question. Is it a strong buy
or is it the next Trade Desk? And this
is where I was going.
The chart's not going to tell you that,
and I think some of it is sentiment.
It's like I'm not saying they're the
exact same company, but it falls in the
same kind of area.
And people got burned on Trade Desk, and
I kind of have to wonder like do people
think this is the next Trade Desk? Cuz
Trade Desk was great till it wasn't.
And I I even said in in a recent chart
day,
I'm not buying AppLovin. Even if it
comes down, I'm probably not going to
buy any because
I'm nervous about Trade Desk. Not the
same time, the risk reward looks really
strong. This R3 Fibonacci is 648.
Of course, there's no guarantee it's
going to go there. It just the risk
reward setup doesn't look bad at all.
This S3 is 251.
Could it go down there? It could, but it
probably holds up a little higher than
that is my guess. If I look at
April 2025,
the stock got down to $200.
And then recent lows March and April, it
got to about 350, 360.
You know, so could it come down to like
200? It could. It probably has new floor
at 250 on this S3.
And it might even hold 300 or 325.
But, I I lack a ton of conviction
because
it kind of feels like the sentiment's
that way. And And remember, sentiment's
60 to 70% of the short-term movement,
and sentiment can linger for years. Look
at the PayPals of the world and so on.
So, I just don't have like a pound the
table. This is not one of our top
high conviction stocks or anything. If
you look at our best of best of breed
list,
and it's just not one I'm personally
buying right here, but I do think it it
could be an opportunity for the right
person.
Uh because if it does go back to even
this R3, that's considerable upside. It
all-time high 738. I mean, it's trading
at 335, so you can do the math, right?
But, definitely be careful. I think it's
a little bit more speculative, but with
all that said, the numbers
look really good.
You know, the numbers look really
strong. So,
it's going to be hard to say
um you know, how it all kind of pans
out, but
AppLovin's one to take a look at. Uber
is holding this 67 or so yesterday, I
think it got to. It's down 20% in the
past year.
It's only up 56%. I got to say only, but
if you look at a lot of tech stocks that
have done better than 56%. Now, if you
look at ARK um
as an example,
>> [laughter]
>> if you look at this over the last 5
years, um this is down 38%. So, I guess
Uber still is quite a bit better at a
positive 55% versus a negative
45% or whatever.
So, if I look at
Uber earnings,
you can see that we had non-GAAP EPS
81 cents beat by 1 cent. Revenue
This is 14.19 billion, missed by 70
million. It's only 11.7% growth.
And this is where I went into Discord
yesterday, also made a I made an
exclusive video on Patreon.
And it broke down Uber. So, if you
haven't seen that, it's right here. You
can go take a look at it. It's on the
Patreon page. You're not in our
community, you want to be in Discord,
you want access to all this, go to
patreon.com/firedupwealth
and join us. There's a few seats left.
But, Uber I explained yesterday at 11:00
a.m.
Another good quarter overall. Here's the
numbers. You can pause and read it if
you want. I want to get to the skinny.
Number one, they generated 10.1 billion
dollars of free cash flow. This reminds
me a lot of Airbnb, how it was just
printing money and nobody cared. The
stock just kind of stayed in that same
range. Uber's been kind of staying in
that 65-75 range, it seems like forever,
right?
They also ended the quarter with 5.4
billion in unrestricted cash and cash
equivalents and investments 12.5
billion. Overall,
the balance sheet looks good. The
company's doing well.
The growth was a little bit slower.
And
the thing about it is is this is purely
optical. It's a headwind on the revenue.
And I think the market didn't understand
right right away, which is why it
knee-jerked and sold off. And then as
analysts kind of figured it out and
you know, Wall Street figured it out, I
think.
You You saw some buyers come back in.
But this is what happened. So there's an
accounting change because of UK tax VAT
rule changes. This took effect in early
2026.
And essentially, it's called the taxi
tax. I'm not going to read through all
this. You can pause it.
But it's going to change how the revenue
is recognized. And so it simply moves
driver payments from cost of revenue to
reduction of revenue or contra revenue.
If you're not an accounting major, don't
worry. You don't need to be. It does
help
some. It's actually good and bad because
it gives you biases because you're
always focused on just
the quantitative data and not the
qualitative. And if you're trying to
growth be a growth investor, it's an art
not a science. And qualitative is a big
part of the story. And so a lot of
people that are accountants generally
um will buy stocks based on fundamental
And there's nothing wrong with value
investing, but when accountants try to
get into growth investing,
I haven't seen many of them do well
because of those biases. Fun fact.
Gross profit, operating income, adjusted
EBITDA, free cash flow, and the actual
economics of the business are completely
unchanged. Gross bookings, the metrics
that reflects the real platform volume
growth,
grew at 22 to 24%. Trips drove 18%.
So if someone is purely
reacting to this report, this headline,
on 12% growth looking soft, it's a
distorted number, and they probably
don't understand that. And most people
don't. Traders don't. They just
knee-jerk. They see a headline and they
go sell it.
But these numbers are good. You look at
mobility, 20%. Delivery, 25%. You know,
freight 25%.
The company's doing well. Right?
So, Uber is one. If you don't own this
one, I think there's a case for this in
autonomous vehicles. We've covered this
extensively in the private community. We
did a 2026 conference video series on
physical AI and robotics that talked
about companies like Nvidia and Tesla,
also Uber. Now, Uber could be a player
in this space
with robo taxis and being kind of that
app that contact to connect people
to robo taxis, right?
So, Tesla's going to do its own thing.
Waymo's doing its own thing, but could
it be a three-headed It's hard to say,
but Uber has lots and lots of volume.
People like ecosystems that they're used
to using. It's the same thing with AI
winners. It's going to be ecosystems,
things like
Google and Apple and Microsoft, things
that are you you you're used to using
that businesses, enterprises are used to
using. Those are going to be the
ultimate winners of AI. And we've seen
that
recently here. We saw some data from the
street talking about how the return on
investments actually coming to fruition
with these companies like Microsoft,
right?
But Uber updated fibs. You've got S2 at
6397, S3 5980. Looks like buyers came in
above this $65 level.
Um I like this stock, especially if it's
65 or less. If it got to 59, I really I
do like it, but it's not one I have high
conviction on where I'm like loading up
the truck. It's I maybe a 2% position or
something like that. It's not going to
be a big position and it's in the
community portfolio, not in the main.
Now, did it also report earnings down
15%? And that might alarm you, but I
remind you that this is SaaS. And so,
most people aren't going to understand
it because it's going to have something
like a high PE ratio 116 here.
You generally look at EV and CM revenue.
It is recurring revenue.
These have high beta. They constantly go
up and down 10, 20, 30% a day. Most
people, especially new investors, should
avoid these kind of stocks because they
are highly volatile. they have high
beta.
But overall it was a good earning. 65
cents beat by 7 cents, 35.4% growth on
1.12 revenue billion.
And you know, if you look at
profitability-wise, it's SaaS, so it's
going to have
pretty solid gross profit margin, about
80%. You know, growth 25s and 30s. And
of course valuation, you look at EV and
TM revenue.
If you're looking at traditional
metrics, and this is again where like
accountants might look at this and say,
"Well, I have to use a PE ratio." Well,
this isn't your Huckleberry.
That's not how you value these kind of
stocks because
think about it, the the revenue is
recurring. If you've ever been in sales,
the hardest thing is going out every
single quarter and starting from zero.
SaaS companies don't have to do that.
The CrowdStrikes of the world. Now,
companies like Snowflake are
consumption-based. I can go down a
rabbit hole. I used to work in software
for a decade. I won't bore you to death.
But DataDog is still expensive.
And this is one I just trimmed. I I
literally just trimmed some couple days
ago.
Um not at the perfect high, but you
know, 20% higher than it is right now
kind of a thing. It's up 74% in the past
year. It's only up 80% in the past 5
years. I say only because 74% in 1 year.
I'm going to explain why the stock is
going higher.
Before I do that, let's look at a chart.
And I can show you Anytime you see
orange, by the way, these are previous
chart days. Yellow is today's chart day.
I I And we're not doing chart day but
it'd be today's presentation. I don't
think I explained that earlier.
So, DataDog, if I look at this,
big Fibonacci range, 302. And there was
a chance, you know, if the if the
earnings went went well, you could see
it 300 plus.
But there was a much higher probability
it dropped 20% than pop 20% based on
where it was at. If you've been
following these for a while, I've been
investing in these companies for many
years. Most of them since like IPO
stage. I was in software for 10 years. I
was buying these kind of stocks when the
market didn't unders- you know, market
still doesn't understand them, but most
This wasn't a household name. And
CrowdStrike wasn't a household name and
so forth.
If I look at the 200-day simple moving
average, this is 169. Most of our buys
have been, you know, like in the '70s.
If you can see our cost basis in the
main, 71, 79 in the community portfolio.
I have a hard time paying even 237, but
it's obviously a much better price than
where it was just at at 292.
I think that the reason it's going
higher is because if I look at OpenAI
and I look at Claude,
these companies, these LM companies, are
using DataDog almost exclusively for
observability.
And so that is why the stock market's
been interested in this because it is
kind of part of that AI trade. It has AI
observability. It's also getting more
into cybersecurity, and cybersecurity is
going to be more resilient than than,
you know, SaaS companies that are
outside of that cyber space, right?
So those are what, six, three, four,
five, six stocks that are at least
interesting to look at, some thoughts on
it. The only stock that I'm buying right
now on the list is MercadoLibre.
Recently, we bought some names like
AAOI,
Oracle. We were buying Microsoft when it
was below 400, you know, 350 to 400.
Most of what I'm buying right now is
opportunistic. Um, you know, I just
showed you the stat earlier about how if
you're buying all-time highs, statistics
say it can go higher. At the same time,
I do stay disciplined to a blueprint,
and I have millions of dollars invested
in the stock market. If I didn't already
have that, I might buy differently. In
other words, if I'm just building a
portfolio and it's all cash, and I'm new
to this, I might be doing things
different than if I've got a bunch of
stocks and I'm sitting on some cash, but
I'm millions of dollars actually in the
market, right? So I would say do what's
best for you. I'm here to try to help
you be a better investor, and if this
kind of content is helpful, and you're
new here, subscribe to the channel,
click that bell to make sure you get
notifications for the next one, and drop
me a like, drop me a comment. It does
help the algo and helps out the channel.
I appreciate you very much. Have a great
rest of your day. Take care.